Guide to the Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archives ca. 1990-1997 MSS 86 MSS 086
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Author Files
  - Subseries B: Serpent's Tail author files
    - Rose, Cynthia--Living in America, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 473)
    - Rowe, Marsha--Sacred Space, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 474)
    - Rowe, Marsha--Sex and the City, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 475)
    - Rowe, Marsha--So Very English, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 476)
    - Rulfo, Juan, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 477)
    - Russell, Mary--Please Don't Call It Soviet Georgia, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 478)
    - Saer, Juan Jose--The Event, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 479)
    - Saer, Juan Jose--Nobody Nothing Never, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 480)
    - Saer, Juan Jose--The Witness, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 481)
    - Sander, Helke--The Three Women K, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 482)
    - Sanza, Silvia--Alex Wants to Call It Love, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 483)
    - Sanza, Silvia--Twice Real, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 484)
    - Schmidt, Susan--Out of America, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 485)
    - Schmidt, Susan--Winging It, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 486)
    - Scott, Mary--Not in Newburg, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 487)
    - Scott, Mary--Nudists May Be Encountered, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 488)
    - Segrave, Elisa--Junky's Christmas, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 489)
    - Smith, Rupert--Physique, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 490)
    - Smith / Hyde--Eagle and Crow, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 491)
    - Smoke Signals: Stories of London, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 492)
    - Srivastava, Atima--Transmission, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 493)
    - Tillman, Lynne--Absence Makes the Heart, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 494)
    - Tillman, Lynne--Cast In Doubt, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 495)
    - Tillman, Lynne--general, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 496)
    - Tillman, Lynne--Haunted Houses, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 497)
    - Tillman, Lynne--Motion Sickness, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 498)
    - Tn, Colm--The South, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 499)
    - Toop, David--Ocean of Sound, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 500)
    - Toop, David--Rap Attack 2, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 501)
    - Tondelli, Pier Vittorio--Separate Rooms, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 502)
    - Tremblay, Michel--The Fat Woman Next Door I s Pregnant, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 503)
    - Tremblay, Michel--Making Room, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 504)
    - Valenzuela, Luisa--The Lizard's Tail, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 505)
    - Valenzuela, Luisa--Open Door, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 506)
    - Vega, Ana Lydia--True and False Romances, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 507)
    - Veronese, David--Jana, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 508)
    - Wakefield, Tom--Lot's Wife, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 509)
    - Wakefield, Tom--Secret Lives, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 510)
    - Wakefield, Tom--The Ten Commandments, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 511)
    - Wakefield, Tom--The Variety Artistes, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 512)
    - Walker, George F.--Shared Anxiety, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 513)
    - Walser, Robert--Institute Benjamenta, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 514)
    - Walser, Robert--The Walk, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 515)
    - Weiss, Ernst--The Aristocrat (Translations), undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 516)
    - West, Paul--Lord Byron's Doctor, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 517)
    - Wilkinson, Margaret--Ocean Avenue, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 518)
    - Wilmer, Valerie--As Serious As Your Life, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 519)
    - Wittig, Susan Albert--Thyme of Death, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 520)
    - Wodin, Natascha--Once I Lived, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 521)
    - Wright, Lawrence--Remembering Satan, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 522)
- Series II: Business and administrative files
  - Accounts--A list and fax list, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounts--Borders, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Account correspondence, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Account correspondence, 1995; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accounts--Tower / Koen, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Account visits--east coast, fall, 1995; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Account visits--west coast, fall, 1995; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advertising--ad placement, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advertising--ad placement / correspondence, 1995; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advertising--ad rate cards, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advertising--ad tearsheets, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Advertising--ad tearsheets, 1995; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Advertising--logos, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Broadart, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Budget--ST, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget--ST, 1994; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Burroughs--limited edition, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Catalog production--fall, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Catalog production--spring, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Commune, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Communication mailing, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Consortium Book Sales and Distribution (CBSD), undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - CBSD catalogue--spring, 1997; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - CBSD catalogue--fall, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CBSD catalogue--spring, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - CBSD correspondence, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - CBSD correspondence, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CBSD correspondence, 1995; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - CBSD--Exact Change for fall 1996 catalogue, 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - CBSD--Exact Change, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - CBSD marketing plan / sales conference booklets, 1996-1997; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - CBSD marketing plan / sales conference booklets, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Copy editors / freelance, undated; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence--Atlas Press, 1996; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence--Atlas Press, 1995-1994; 31142040617030 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence--editorial, 1996; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence--editorial, 1995; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence--editorial, 1994; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence--editorial, 1994; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence--editorial, 1994; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence--editorial, 1992-1993; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence--general, 1996; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence--general, 1995; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence--general, 1995; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence--general, 1995; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence--general, 1995; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence--general, 1995; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence--general, 1993; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence--rep, 1996; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence--Rex Ray, 1996; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence--Silverberg, Ira, undated; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1996; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1996; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1996; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1995; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1994; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1994; 31142040617048 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1993; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1993; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence-U.K., 1992; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Donations, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Events--fall, 1996; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Events--spring, 1996; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Events--All Girls Tour, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Events--Bomb reading, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Events--checklist, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Events--Cortez, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Events--Swine's Wedding, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Galley production--Home, Slow Death, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Galley production--Nearly Roadkill, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Galley production--Swine's Wedding, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Galley production--Sterling-Pierce, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Library of Congress, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Mailing houses, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Manuscript submission log, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Marketing research--academic, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Marketing research--book clubs, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Marketing research--gay / lesbian, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Marketing research--Latin America, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Marketing research--libraries, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Marketing research--misc, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Marketing research--mystery, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Marketing research--translations, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - McClelland & Stewart, 1996; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - McClelland & Stewart, 1995; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Meeting minutes, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Midnight Classics--general, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Midnight Classics--rights research, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Midnight Classics--rights research, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Muze, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Office procedures, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Office procedures, undated; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Permissions, 1996; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Permissions, 1993-1995; 31142040617055 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Printers, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Production info (promo materials), undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Production updates, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Production updates, 1995; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Publication schedule--spring, 1997; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Publication schedule--fall, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Publication schedule--spring, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Publication schedule--spring 1996 tips, 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Publication schedule and tip sheets, 1994-1995; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Remainders, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Requests--academic, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Requests--academic, 1995; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Requests--academic, 1994; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Requests--review, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Requests--review, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Resume-intern, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Resume, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Resume, 1995; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Rights--misc, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Services, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - 10th Anniversary, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - 10th Anniversary--tattoo info, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Trade shows--ABA, 1997; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Trade shows--ABA, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Trade shows--ABA, 1995; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Trade shows--hotel info for ABA, 1995; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Trade shows--Frankfurt Bookfair, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Trade shows--London International Bookfair, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Trade shows--MLA, Dec., 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Trade shows--NEBA, fall, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Trade shows--Regionals, 1996; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Trade shows--Salon du Livre (Paris bookfair), undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Travel--general, undated; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Travel--west coast, fall, 1995; 31142040617063 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Website, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Website--Amazon, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Website--Bookwire, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Website--computer stuff, clippings, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Website--consultants, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Website--Davis, Geoff, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Website--domain registrations, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Website--Echo, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Website--NY local servers, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Website--on-line marketing, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Website--training (computer--software / internet), undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Website-U.K./SF internet services, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Window contest, undated; 31142040617071 (Box 5, Folder 141)
- Series III: Manuscripts
  - Acker, Kathy--essays (copyedited), undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acker, Kathy--essays, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acker, Kathy--essays, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acker, Kathy--nonfiction / essays, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Acker, Kathy--nonfiction / essays, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acker, Kathy--nonfiction / essays, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acker, Kathy--nonfiction / essays, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acker, Kathy--nonfiction / essays, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Acker, Kathy, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bornstein / Sullivan--Nearly Roadkill, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Collins, Art, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cooper, Dennis--Little Caesar, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cortez, Jayne--Somewhere in Advance of Nowhere (advance uncorrected proof), undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cortez, Jayne--Somewhere (first corrections), undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dlugos, Tim--Powerless, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fichte, Hubert--The Leatherman, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Flanagan, Bob--Book of Medicine, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Flanagan, Bob--Sick, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Galas, Diamanda--The Shit of God (final corrections), undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Galas, Diamanda--The Shit of God (final), undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Galas, Diamanda--The Shit of God, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Galas, Diamanda--The Shit of God, undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Galas, Diamanda--The Shit of God (text corrections), undated; 31142040617089 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Galas, Diamanda--The Shit of God, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Galas, Diamanda--The Shit of God, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Giorno, John, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Hemphill, Essex--Vital Signs, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Home, Stewart--Blow Job, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Home, Stewart--Slow Death (advance uncorrected proof), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - House, Richard--Bruiser (final), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - House, Richard--Bruiser (final), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - House, Richard--Bruiser (copy edit #2), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - House, Richard--Bruiser (copy edit), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - House, Richard--Bruiser (next to final), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - House, Richard--Bruiser (original MS), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - House, Richard, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Indiana, Gary--Let It Bleed (advance uncorrected proof), undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Indiana, Gary--Let It Bleed, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Indiana, Gary--Rent Boy, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Kennedy, Pagan--from Stripping & Other Stories, undated; 31142040617097 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Kertess, Klaus--South Brooklyn Casket Company (final), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Kertess, Klaus--South Brooklyn Casket Company (with corrections), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Kertess, Klaus--South Brooklyn Casket Company (edited), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Kertess, Klaus--South Brooklyn Casket Company, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Kertess, Klaus, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Kertess, Klaus, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Kordi, Gohar--An Iranian Odyssey, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Lambert, Gavin--The Goodly People, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Lambert, Gavin--Running Time, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Lambert, Gavin--The Slide Area, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Lerner, Jonathan, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Mueller, Cookie--Ask Dr. Mueller (corrected proofs), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Mueller, Cookie--Ask Dr. Mueller (proofs), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Mueller, Cookie, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Olsen, M. H.--Passion's Prize, undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Olson, Jenni--The Ultimate Guide to Lesbian (advance uncorrected proof), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Peabody, Richard--A Different Beat (final), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Peabody, Richard--A Different Beat (final), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Peabody, Richard--A Different Beat (edited), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Peabody, Richard--A Different Beat (edited), undated; 31142040617105 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Peabody, Richard--Beat Women, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Peabody, Richard--Beat Women, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Purdy, James [removed and catalogued for Fales Downtown Collection], undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Sapphire--Push, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Shaviro, Steven--Doom Patrols (advance uncorrected proof), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Shaviro, Steven--Doom Patrols (author's corrections), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Shaviro, Steven--Doom Patrols (proofreader's corrections), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Shaviro, Steven--Doom Patrols, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Shaviro, Steven--Doom Patrols, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me (final), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me (editor's corrections--copy), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me (editor's corrections--original), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me at the Bottom of the Pool (proofs), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me (clean copy of proofs), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me, 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me, 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Smith, Jack--Wait for Me (original MS), undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Smith, Jack, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Smith, Jack--writings, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Smith, Jack--writings, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Stone, Laurie--Hump, Perfect Strangers, Water Marks, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Stone, Laurie--Rough Exposures, undated; 31142040617113 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Tillman, Lynne--The Broad Picture (final), undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Tillman, Lynne--The Broad Picture (without copy edits), undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Trocchi, Alexander, undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Trocchi, Alexander, undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Trocchi, Alexander, undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Weiss, Daniel--Swine's Wedding (proof), undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Weiss, Daniel--Swine's Wedding (corrections), undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Weiss, Daniel--Swine's Wedding, undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Weiss, Daniel--Swine's Wedding, undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Weiss, Daniel--Swine's Wedding, undated; 31142040617121 (Box 5, Folder 92)
- Series IV: Production files
  - Ads, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advance book information forms, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Burroughs, William--manuscript, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Burroughs, William--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Burroughs, William--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Burroughs, William--misc, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Burroughs, William--printing, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bush, Catherine, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CIP (Cataloging in Publication) info, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (re: production), undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - First 6, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Glück, Robert--copy, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Glück, Robert--manuscript, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Glück, Robert--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Glück, Robert--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Glück, Robert--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Glück, Robert--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Glück, Robert--misc, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Glück, Robert--printing, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Indiana, Gary--misc, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Indiana, Gary--printing, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Irises, etc, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Kennedy, Pagan--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Kennedy, Pagan--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Kennedy, Pagan--misc, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 25)